♪ You know the night time, darling ♪
♪ night and day ♪
♪ is the right time ♪
♪ to be ♪
♪ night and day ♪
♪ with the one love, now ♪
♪ night and day... ♪
你做的很棒  宝贝
You're doing perfect, baby.
就是这样  很好
That's right. That's good.
给自己倒一杯吧
Pour yourself a little drink.
好的  我会给自己…
Yeah, I will pour myself...
是的  给自己倒一杯吧
Yeah, pour yourself a little drink.
我会给自己倒一杯
I will pour myself a little drink.
佩吉  专注点  看着我
Peg, focus. Look at me and stay focused.
这里  宝贝
- Bunny... - Right here, baby.
我们看到了什么?
What are we seeing, what are we seeing?
我正在努力专注!
I'm trying to focus!
别太用力  佩吉
- Not too hard, peg. - I'm trying to focus!
那些流苏妨碍你了
The tassels are weighing you down.
把上衣脱掉!你得摆脱它们
I think you gotta lose them and take them off!
把衣服脱了!
Take the shirt off!
可以了
I have it, I have it, I have it, I have it.
专注  就是这样
Focus. Right here.
倾斜一点
Tip it a little bit.
哦
Oh!
这不公平!是佩吉害她弄掉的!
That's not fair! Peg made her drop it!
这不算数
That doesn't count.
大吉大利  赢家大收获!
Winner, winner, cigarette dinner!
这不是我的错!等等
That wasn't my fault! Hang on.
-那杯酒是我的 -不  她推倒我头上的杯子
- That is my drink. - No, she pushed it off my head.
-我来喝光吧   -不  我本可以赢的
- I'll finish that. - No, but I can win.
她刚刚推了我一下  不公平!
She just budged me. It's not fair!
我知道你能赢
I know you can win.
-你确定?    - 我都知道
- Mm-Kay. Are you sure? - I know you can...
是的
Mm-Kay. Yeah.
-你弄翻了  这不是我的错 -都洒到我裙子上了
- You dropped it, or was it my fault? - It got on my dress.
♪ Baby ♪
♪ night and day ♪
哦  千万别让那着火!
Oh, don't set it on fire!
迪恩亲爱的
Deanie, sweetheart,
-能请你用烟灰缸吗?  -啥?
- can you please use an ashtray? - What?
那要是沾到地毯  很难清除的
Because if it gets on the rug, it's impossible to get out.
彼得  你妻子喝醉了
Pete, your wife is drunk.
开始胡言乱语
She's babbling nonsense right now.
她也怀孕了  得再喝一杯
And she's pregnant, and so she needs another drink,
这有助于胎儿健康
get that baby healthy.
她应该为胎儿着想!
She should think about the baby!
打扰一下!
- Excuse me, excuse me! - Whoa!
这是随着升职而来的? 你们有看到这个吗?
Did this come with the promotion? You see this?
-看看这个 -你知道吗…
-Look at this man. Look at this. -You know...
法兰克举办过一场典礼 这看上去跟他拥有的一样
Frank did a ceremony. It's just like the one he has.
-真是优雅 -看看吧  看看这人
-So gracious. -Look at this. Look at this man.
亲吻戒指吧  宝贝
Kiss the ring, baby.
这不附带任何条件
This doesn't get into bed.
天啊  看看这对哥们!
Oh, my god. Look at... look at this love!
你现在要亲吻我了吗?
Are you going to kiss me right now?
-是的!
- Yeah, is that... - Mwah!
畅饮时间!
Time for upski downski!
畅饮时间到了!
Upski downski!
人人有份
For you, and for you, and for you, and for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
-剩下的都是我的! -都是你的
- And these are for me! - Those are all for you.
喝光它
Drink 'em all. Drink 'em all.
你可真能喝  也漂亮极了
You drink like a sailor and look like a pin-up doll.
-哦  宝贝 -哦  该死的
- Oh, baby. - Oh, god damn it.
要去兜风吗?
You want to go for a ride?
我快掉出车外了!
I'm slipping out of the car!
我的天啊!
Oh, my god!
轮到你来开
You have to drive.
轮到你 快来驾驶盘
It's your turn. Take the wheel!
-快接过驾驶盘! -天啊  什么?
-Take the wheel! Take the wheel! -Oh, my god! What?
-不  我还没准备好!
- No, I'm not ready! - I've driven us...
天啊! -我开车的次数已够多了
- Oh, my god! - I've driven us more than enough.
爱丽丝  你的驾驶技术更好了
Alice, you're getting so much better.
是的  我感觉自己越来越熟练
I am. I feel better.
你越来越棒了
You're getting so much better.
带我回家吧  爱丽丝
Take me home, Alice.
带我回家
Take me home.
要是蒙上你的眼睛呢?
What if you're blind?
-不  不行! -快啊
- No, I can't! - Now do it. Now do it.
你做的棒极了!
You're doing so good! You're doing so good!
-好的  坐直了 -你能帮帮我吗?
- All right, now straighten up. - Can you help me?
坐直
Straighten up.
做得好
Good job.
邦妮接着说她也想玩…
So then bunny said that she wanted to play, which, mm...
但她从没打过网球
She's never played tennis before, ever.
她一手拿着鸡尾酒 另一手握着球拍
She has a cocktail in one hand, a racket in the other,
杰克…  她一滴酒也没洒出
and, Jack... She didn't spill a drop.
那真是…
It was...
我见过最性感的画面
Quite possibly the sexiest thing I have ever seen.
我很想看你穿网球裙子
I want to see you in a tennis skirt.
天
God...
你说法兰克家中是否真有网球场?
Do you think it's true that frank actually has a tennis court at his house?
-到时候就知道了  不是吗?   -是的
- We'll find out, won't we? - Yeah.
还有  宝贝  你得告诉我…
Oh, and babe, tell me...
这个派对有多少人出席
How many people are gonna be at this party,
我得准备足够的金枪鱼沙拉
because I need to know how much tuna salad to make.
-怎么了? -法兰克不喜欢吃金枪鱼
- What? - Frank doesn't like tuna.
-什么? -他就不喜欢
- What? - He doesn't like it.
你是说真的?
- Are you being serious? - Mm-hm.
宝贝  你为何没告诉我?
Baby, why didn't you tell me?
我打算用这道菜作为主菜
I was planning on it being the centerpiece to my dish.
-爱丽丝  那不能是主菜 -闭嘴
- Alice, not the centerpiece. - Shut up.
糟糕!该死的
Oh, no! Shit.
别问
Don't.
-那是大规模的建筑工程吗? -别问
- Was that a big drill? - Don't.
-还是引发爆炸了? -别问了
- Was that an explosion? - Don't.
那些是开发的先进材料?
- Are those the progressive materials? - Mm-hm.
你可以告诉我  我口风很紧
You can tell me. I'm... I'm really discreet.
-我能保守秘密 -我快迟到了
- I can keep a secret. - I'm going to be late.
你不能离开
No, wait, you... you can't... You can't leave.
为什么不能?
Why not?
因为你感觉不适
'Cause you're not feeling well.
-我感觉不适吗?   -是的  抱歉
- Oh, I'm not? - Yeah, I'm so sorry.
我忘了告诉你 你现在感觉非常不适
I forgot to tell you, but you're not feeling very well.
唯一治疗办法就是一整天留在家里
And the only way to cure it is if we stay home all day,
让我照顾你  亲吻你  替你做饭…
and I tend to you and kiss you and cook for...
不行
- Mm-hm. - No.
-再见 -好吧
- Bye. - Okay.
该死的!杰克  等等!
Oh... Jack, wait!
再见了  好好工作  让我们感到骄傲
Bye-bye. Make us proud.
♪ Do-do-do ♪
♪ I'm comin' home, baby, now ♪
♪ do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ I'm comin' home now right away ♪
♪ do-do-do ♪
♪ I'm comin' home, baby, now ♪
♪ do-do-do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ I'm sorry now I ever went away ♪
♪ do-do-do-do-do ♪
♪ every night and day I go and stay ♪
♪ I'm comin' home, baby ♪
♪ come on home ♪
♪ comin' home, baby, now ♪
♪ you know I'm waitin' here for you ♪
♪ I'm comin' home now ♪
♪ real soon ♪
♪ you've been gone ♪
♪ comin' home, baby, now ♪
♪ you don't know what I'm goin' through ♪
♪ I'm comin' home I know I'm overdue ♪
♪ since you went away ♪
♪ expect me any day ♪
♪ now, real soon ♪ - ♪ now, real soon ♪
♪ I'm comin' home ♪
♪ come on home ♪
胜利项目  第987天
Victory project, day 987.
安全级别为黄色
Security level, yellow.
所有员工在前往胜利总部的途中
All employees in transit to victory headquarters.
所有居民都安然无恙
All residents safe and accounted for.
享受美好的一天  女士们
Enjoy the beautiful day, ladies,
并继续关注法兰克的广播
and stay tuned for frank's radio hour.
♪ Oogum, oogum, boogum ♪
♪ boogum ♪
♪ boogum, now, baby you're castin' your spell on me ♪
♪ I say, oogum, oogum boogum, boogum ♪
♪ Just look at me ♪
♪ when you wear your high-heeled boots ♪
♪ with your hip-hugger suit ♪
彼得让我发誓不能告诉任何人
Peter made me swear not to tell anyone.
他们要在我们屋子后侧 搭建一排全新的房子
So they're gonna build a whole new row of houses behind us,
这样我们会更靠近城镇
so we'll be much closer to town.
真的吗?哇
- Really? Wow. - Mm-hm.
等等  这怎么让你们更靠近城镇?
So wait, how does that make you closer to town?
我们不再是离城镇最远的房子
We won't be furthest from town.
早安  女士们
Good morning, ladies.
早安  雪莉
Good morning, shelley.
我有一些非常令人兴奋的消息
I have some very exciting news.
胜利项目聘请了新职员  比尔约翰逊
The victory project has hired a new employee, bill Johnson,
我邀请了他妻子加入今天的课程
and I've invited his wife to join us today.
各位  请热烈欢迎
Everyone, please give a warm welcome...
维丽特约翰逊
To Violet Johnson.
欢迎你  维丽特
Welcome, Violet.
我们开始吧  进入第一位置
Let's begin. First position.
记住了  女士们  控制中有美态
Remember, ladies, there is beauty in control.
对称中有优雅  我们行动一致
There is grace in symmetry. We move as one.
收腹
Stomach in.
抬起下巴
Chin up.
就是这样
That's it.
玛格丽特当然没去上课
Yeah, of course Margaret wasn't in class.
科林斯医生又到他们家去了
I saw Dr. Collins at their house again.
-不会吧!
No!
-我很惊讶泰德仍有份工作
Honestly shocked Ted still has a job.
-又一次吗?  -从她脖子上解除  费雷德!
- Again? - Unwrap it from her neck, Fred!
-是的 -天啊
- Yeah. - Oh, my god.
-真是可怜的家伙  -我见过她了
- Poor guy. - Oh! I met her.
那位新来的人妻
- Mm! - The new wife.
维丽特
Violet.
她为人如何?
- Mm-hm. - What's she like?
她就像一头美丽又害怕的小鹿
She's like a beautiful, terrified, baby deer.
听说她丈夫是个傻子
Yeah. Apparently, the husband's a real goober.
希望杰克能尽快聘请到人
Well, Jack better recruit somebody soon.
拜托!  迪恩说杰克就快升职了
Please! Dean says Jack's about to get promoted.
-我希望是吧
- I hope so. - Mm-hm.
你们很快就会追上我们了
You're gonna be right behind us.
你为派对准备了什么佳肴?
What are you making for the party?
-我拿手的魔鬼蛋   -天啊
- My deviled eggs. - Oh, my god.
杰克肯定能当上总裁
Jack's gonna be ceo.
麻烦帮我拿一下    够了
Hold this, please. That's it.
我要去跟圣诞老人说了
- I'm calling Santa. - Uh-oh.
-你们让我别无选择 -糟糕
- You give me no choice. - Oh, no.
我必须打给圣诞老人!
I have to call him. I have to!
他给我电话号码是有原因的
That's why Santa gave me his number.
他说你们不听话时就打给他
He said I had to call if you were bad.
我也不想的
I'm calling him. I wish I had a choice.
-把那个给我   -但我们已经停止了!
- Give me that. - But we stopped!
不  快把那个给我!
- Give me that. No. Give it to me!
重要的是你在艰难时刻如何应对
All that matters is how you respond in those moments.
我相信你会向自己
I trust that you will prove to yourself,
也向所有曾质疑过你的人证明
to everyone who has ever doubted you,
你值得拥有你所向往的人生
that you are worthy of the life you desire.
我们明天见
Until tomorrow.
♪ You don't remember me ♪
♪ but I remember you ♪
♪ 'twas not so long ago ♪
♪ you broke my heart in two ♪
♪ tears on my pillow ♪
♪ pain in my heart ♪
♪ caused by you ♪
♪ you ♪
哦  该死的
Oh, shit.
…因为我们选择留下
'Cause we choose to stay.
嗨
Hi.
♪ In the sweet and same old way ♪
♪ I fall in love again ♪
♪ as I did then... ♪
你今天过得怎么样?
How was your day?
现在好多了
- So much better now. - Mm-hm.
我做了烤肉
I made a roast.
-还有呢?  -土豆泥
- What else? - Mashed potatoes.
-还有呢?    -青豆
- What else? - Green beans.
还有呢?
What else?
酿西红柿
Stuffed tomatoes.
还有呢?
What else?
♪ As I did then ♪
♪ deep in the dark your kiss will thrill me ♪
♪ like days of old ♪
♪ lighting the spark of love ♪
♪ that fills me with dreams untold ♪
♪ each day I pray for evening ♪
♪ just to be with you ♪
♪ Life could be a dream life could be a dream ♪
♪ do do do do, sh-boom ♪
♪ life could be a dream ♪ - ♪ sh-boom ♪
♪ if I could take you up in paradise up above... ♪
大家都穿得好暴露
There's so much... skin.
你不如去找哥哥吧?
Ooh, why don't you go find your brother, okay?
你得停止哼那首歌
Okay, you have to stop humming that song.
-是什么歌?  -我不知道
- What is it? - I don't know.
还指望你告诉我
I was hoping you could tell me.
我这几天一直在想这首歌
It's been stuck in my head for days.
也许是儿歌  你孩子唱过的歌?
Maybe it's a children's song. Something your kids sing?
不是的  我没有小孩
Oh, no, I don't have children.
别让我从头开始说
- Oh. - Mm. Don't get me started.
这不在我们的规划中 我们只想享受人生
It's just not what we want. We're having fun.
我就住在她家隔壁 你无法想象我听到的声音
I live next door. You wouldn't believe the things I've heard.
她们像在度过永久的蜜月期
It's like they're on a perpetual honeymoon.
不  杰克跟爱丽丝 只愿意在彼此身上花时间
No, Jack and Alice only have time for each other.
我们没打算生孩子
It's not what we want.
再说  邦妮的孩子也喜欢我多过她
Plus, bunny's kids like me more than her, anyway.
这倒是真的  真气人
That's true, it's infuriating.
我想三个孩子就够了
I think three is a perfect number.
但比尔要四个
Bill wants four.
有了第一个孩子后  多几个都一样
Well, once you have one, it's all the same.
有了第二个孩子…
Having a second...
爱丽丝  维丽特应该生几个孩子?
Alice, how many babies should Violet have?
哦  至少七个吧
Oh, at least seven.
（胜利项目）
（只限员工）
（通往胜利总部）
天啊  你去哪了?
Christ. Where have you been?
我避开跟他人交谈都快成为专家了
I've turned avoiding talking to other people into an olympic sport.
-这地方棒极了! -你还没见到更棒的部分
- This place is incredible! - You haven't seen half of it.
他们的浴缸面积大得不像话
I could sleep in their bathtub and they'd never find me.
我想肯定是  嗨!
I'm sure! Hi!
嘿!
Hey!
你们有兴趣来杯鸡尾酒吗?
May we interest you in a cocktail?
-好啊  谢谢    -是的  我非常有兴趣
- Uh, yes, you may. Thank you. - Yes, very interested.
-再见 -再见
- Bye-bye. - Bye.
谢谢
Thank you.
-他们令我害怕 -他们好诡异
- They terrify me. - They're so creepy.
他们肯定倒着睡觉
I feel like they sleep upside down.
他们每天都穿着相配的衣服吗?
- Do they wear matching outfits every day? - Oh!
这个小怪胎调的曼哈顿 是我喝过最美味的
That little weirdo makes the best Manhattan I've ever had.
我们在海岛度蜜月
We honeymooned in sea island.
哦
Oh!
-什么? -我们在海岛度蜜月
- What? - We honeymooned in sea island.
真的?
Seriously?
你有在多米尼克用餐吗?
Yeah, did you eat at Dominick's?
我感到有点不自在
I was a little nervous.
花了一段时间才适应
Took a while to get used to things.
安顿下来需要一些时间
Yeah. It takes a minute to settle in.
但一切会逐渐变得容易
- Yeah. - But it gets easier, though.
确实如此
- It does. Yeah. - Well, it...
我很高兴能来这里
I'm just really excited to be here.
-我好兴奋…  -我们还真看不出
- So excited, I can't even... - We couldn't tell.
说真的  刚到这里时  我感到很迷茫
To be honest, I've been out of it since we arrived.
是的
Yeah.
比尔说是因为时差
- Bill says it's the jetlag. - Mm-hm.
但我就是提不起劲
It's all just been a bit of a blur.
沙漠的空气不同  你慢慢会适应的
It's the desert air. You'll get used to it.
科林斯医生也这么说
That's what Dr. Collins said, too.
他很热心  前来探访我们
He was so sweet to stop by.
-杰克  你的专长是什么?  -我是一名技术工程师
- And, Jack, you're... - -I'm a technical engineer.
她应该跟我们一同去逛街
She should come shopping with us.
我跟迪恩和泰德不同部门
A different department than, uh, Dean and Ted.
严格来说是个更糟糕 也不怎么重要的部门
Yeah, technically a worse, less important department.
我没什么机会能跟法兰克交谈
I haven't really gotten to talk to frank very much.
法兰克无需跟你交谈
Frank doesn't have to talk to you.
哦  很抱歉  我无意…
Oh, I'm sorry. I didn't...
你不知道他有多非凡
You have no idea how extraordinary he is.
也非常有本事
Or what he can do.
你能认识他就很幸运了
You're lucky to even know who he is,
更别说是身处在他的房子
let alone be standing in his house.
我只是感到很兴奋  抱歉
I'm just excited. I'm sorry.
我过于兴奋了
I was just excited. Okay.
哦!各位  走吧
- Oh! Guys, guys, guys. Go, go, go, go. - Ooh, here we go.
-这里吗? -是的  你先吧
- This way? - Yeah, you should go in front.
请大家聚集一起
Gather 'round, everyone.
我们通常没什么机会
Now, usually, we don't have the opportunity
能在家中欢迎新来的夫妇
to welcome couples in our home.
但在这个场合  我们迫不及待想
But on this occasion, we just couldn't wait
欢迎我们最新的居民
to celebrate our newest residents.
比尔和维丽特
Bill, Violet...
我为你们感到高兴
I am so happy for you,
你们能跟我丈夫学习
that you get to learn from my husband...
并且参与这个使命
And join this mission
成为这个大家庭的一份子
and become a part of this family.
法兰克建造了一个非常独特的东西
Frank has built something truly special.
他在这里创造的东西…
What he's created out here, it's...
十分与众不同
It's a different way.
也是一条更好的道路
A better way.
-而我们只有彼此… -我们为何来这里?
- And we only have each other... - Why are we here?
我们得立即离开
Let's go, right now.
我们不该来这里
We shouldn't be here.
那是怎么回事?
What was that?
大家冷静下来
Now, now.
玛格丽特和泰德 正在经历一段艰难的时期
Margaret and Ted are going through a difficult time.
玛格丽特的发问是对的 这也是一个很好的问题
Margaret's question is right. It is the good question to ask.
我们该死的为何在这里?
Why the hell are we here?
毕竟  眼前这片景观…
Why, when this landscape can seem so...
贫瘠  充满灰尘  甚至…
Barren, so hard, so dusty, so...
一文不值?
Worthless?
我们为何不逃离这里?
Why not run?
为何不返回安逸的现况?
Why not go back to safety, status quo,
那才是我们应该拥有的安全家园
where it's safe, where we should be?
不  因为我和大家一样 都选择了坚守立场
No, I choose... We choose to stand our ground.
对吗?
Right?
我们必须更努力寻找  更深入挖掘
To look harder, to dig deeper.
才能激发出纯粹也无拘无束的潜力
To mine that pure,unbridled potential.
形成那颗拥有无限价值的宝石
That gem of limitless and unimaginable value.
我们很容易因为眼前的事物而分心
It's just too easy to get distracted by what seems.
更困难的是能做到“勇敢”…
Much more difficult, "braver," I would say...
去寻找那无限可能的前景
To search for what could be.
迪恩
- Dean... - Hm?
进步的敌人是什么?
What is the enemy of progress?
-混乱 -是的
- Chaos. - Yes.
这是个很糟糕的词语  混乱
Nasty word. Chaos.
那无情的敌人  混乱
Merciless foe, that chaos.
精力不能集中  创新受阻
Energy unfocused, innovation hindered,
希望被扼杀而伟大也被伪装起来
hope strangled, greatness disguised.
我在每个人身上都看出了无限可能
I see greatness in each one of you.
我很清楚知道你们是谁
I know exactly who you are.
-我们在做什么? -改变世界
- What are we doing? - Changing the world.
没错
That's right.
我环顾四周  看到了 我在这里的另一个原因
I look around, I see another reason why I'm here.
曾经是陌生脸孔的陌生人 现在全都变成了…
Once unfamiliar faces, strangers, one and all, now...
一个勇敢的大家庭
One brave family.
像科林斯医生一样的人
Men like Dr. Collins.
他和我一起建立了这个社区
One of our first, who built this community with me.
谢谢你的远见  科林斯医生
Thank you, Dr. Collins for your vision.
还有像比尔这样的冒险家 我们最新加入的无畏探险家
And adventurers like bill, our newest intrepid explorer.
这位年轻勇敢的鲁滨逊
This brave, young Robinson crusoe,
选择加入我们的冒险
who's choosing to join us on this adventure.
比尔  谢谢你成为 我们在这方面的合作伙伴
Bill, thank you for being our partner in this.
也谢谢你  维丽特 作为他在这里的生活伴侣
And thank you, Violet, for being his partner in this.
没有你  他无法做到这一点
He could not do this without you.
在场的所有人妻…
All of you wives...
我们男人有众多要求
We men, we ask a lot.
我们祈求能拥有力量 一个可以哭泣的肩膀…
We ask for strength, a shoulder to cry on...
餐桌上有食物  一个干净的房子
Food at home, a house cleaned,
更重要的  是自由裁量权
and discretion, above all else. And that...
而这些都很难达成
That's very difficult.
你是我最坚强的后盾
You are my rock.
没有你就没有我
I would not be here without you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你们全都退下吧
You're all dismissed.
♪ Baby, baby, baby... ♪
杰克?
Jack?
-玛格丽特 -他们把我藏在这里
- Margaret. - They're hiding me in here.
哦  给我们一点时间 爱丽丝  她会没事的
Oh, give us a second, Alice. She'll be fine.
我并非没事
I'm not fine.
这里的一切都并非没事
Nothing is fine.
-她只是需要好好睡一觉 -我根本没法睡
- She just needs to sleep. - I don't sleep.
我一直做噩梦
I have bad dreams.
♪ I wanna love ya love ya, baby ♪
♪ if I live to 99! ♪
♪ Just give me five, ten... ♪
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我在想为何会选择这条领带
I wonder why I chose this tie.
我很喜欢你的领带
I like your ties.
不行
No.
外头有很多人
There are so many people outside.
杰克  有很多人
Jack, there are so many people.
外头有很多人
There are so many people outside.
在双打比赛中让他惊叹不已 他肯定会对你爱不释手
Wow him in a doubles game. He'll 40-love this look.
是的
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
能把费用记到迪恩账上吗?
Can you charge that to Dean's account?
我仍没法想象这里任何地方都能记账
I still can't believe we can just charge, everywhere.
对  但胜利社区也有钱买不到的东西
Yes, but victory has things money can't buy. - Mm-hm.
这倒是真的  这里无需 担心天气也不用学会开车
It's true, you don't have to worry about the weather or learning to drive. Ugh.
-我很喜欢开车 -不
- I love driving. - No.
你只是喜欢杰克教你开车
You love Jack teaching you to drive.
这是你们之间的调情
That's foreplay.
我们谈谈宾客名单吧  凯西和鲍勃有被邀到法兰克家吗?
Circle back to the guest list. Were Kathy and Bob at frank's?
-好像有吧 -真的?
- I think so. - Really?
哇  这听起来很随机  对吧?
Wow, so it just seems very random, right?
那些被邀请和不被邀请的人
Who is invited and who isn't.
这与资历或成功无关
It has nothing to do with seniority, or success,
也不关系到受欢迎程度  对吧?
or even being well-liked, right?
谁准备好潜入夏天了?
Splish-splash. Who's ready to dive into summer?
-购买 -那真难看
- Charge that. - Hideous.
-听说玛格丽特当众吵闹 -我的天啊
- I heard Margaret made a scene. - Oh, my god.
-她往别人脸上泼酒? Threw a drink in someone's face?
什么?没这回事 没发生这种事
What? No. That did not happen.
她只是很难过
She was upset.
那十分丢人  她会害泰德被解雇的
It was humiliating, and she's gonna get Ted fired.
哦
Oh.
要是彼得被解雇
If Peter got fired...
我会自杀的
I'd kill myself.
我没在跟你们开玩笑 我没法在别的地方居住
Not kidding. Can't live anywhere else.
玛格丽特在经历非常艰难的时期
Margaret is just having a really hard time.
她能怪谁?
Whose fault is that?
我知道  我还是很替她难过
I know. I still feel bad for her.
当然  那是一场可怕的意外
Of course. It was a terrible accident.
那并不是一场意外
It wasn't an accident.
邦妮  别说了
Bunny, stop. Come on.
我无意冒犯  我知道她曾是你朋友
I don't want to be rude. I know that she was your friend.
她还正常时也算是我们的朋友
She was our friend, when she was normal.
但她接着像是发了疯似的
And then she lost her mind.
她把儿子带到那片沙漠
She took her son out into that desert.
-她以为自己看到了某些东西 -她产生了幻觉
- She thought she saw something. - She hallucinated.
至于发生了什么  我们也不清楚
Well, it wasn't exactly clear as to what... happened.
她像我们所有人一样 知道那么做有多危险
She knew how dangerous it was, just like we all do.
他们对我们的唯一要求 就是留在这里
The one thing they ask of us is to stay here,
这里才安全
where it's safe.
但她还是拖着那小男孩到那鬼地方
But still, she dragged that little boy out into the middle of god-knows-what.
他们不要我们到外头去
If they don't want us going out there,
肯定有他们的原因
they have their reasons.
他们找到她时…
So when they found her...
她独自一人
She was alone.
他们始终没找到他
They never found him.
哦
Oh.
我知道他死掉了
I knew he died, I...
但我没意识到…
I just hadn't realized...
她声称他们带走了他  只为惩罚她
She claims they took him to punish her.
那些男人和他们专注的无趣事物
Boys and their toys.
至少我们知道他们是真的在做事
Least we know they're getting work done.
你说他们在外头到底在做些什么?
What do you think they're really doing out there?
-你这是什么意思? -我知道他们总是说…
- What do you mean? - I mean, I know what they say...
是为了“开发先进材料”
You know, "development of progressive materials,"
但彼得有时候像是在暗示
but, sometimes Peter insinuates
他们实际上是在制造武器
that they're actually making weapons.
而这一切都在暗地里进行
And that it's all happening underground,
-因为法兰克发现了… -佩吉
- because frank discovered... - Peg.
抱歉
Sorry.
大家来这里的目的 是因为相信这个使命
We're all here because we believe in the mission.
是的
Yes.
我们也有同样重要  不可或缺的工作
We have jobs too, that are just as important, just as vital.
我们留在家支持并照顾他们
What we do at home, supporting them,taking care of them.
没有我们  他们没法在外头改变世界
Without that, they couldn't be out there changing the world.
大家都专注于你所做的牺牲
Everyone focuses on the sacrifices
通过追求你想要的
you make by going after what you want.
你们得专注于静止不动而做出的牺牲
I want you to focus on the sacrifices you make by standing still.
通过不去追求那些你得放弃的事
By not going after what you know you are owed by giving up,
满足于较为简易的人生
and taking the smaller version of your life.
牺牲不仅需要勇气
Sacrifice doesn't just take courage,
也需要有信念  能够大声说出
it takes faith, saying,
“我会忍受这般痛苦  伤害及努力
"I will stand this pain, this hurt, this effort,
因为我知道我想要的 就在另一端等着我”
knowing that what I want is waiting on the other side."
牺牲某样东西是可怕的
It's scary to sacrifice something.
但陷在恐惧之中什么也不做 牺牲的将是更多
But you're sacrificing something more by sitting in that fear.
我们明天见
Until tomorrow.
（胜利小镇有轨电车 放松乘搭!）
♪ is to love, love, love him ♪
♪ just to see him smile ♪
（胜利社区第二阶段 即将推出）
♪ to know, know, know him... ♪
今天没去逛街吗?
No shopping today, huh?
什么?
What?
哦  我问你今天没去逛街?
Oh, I said, no shopping today, huh?
哦  没有
Oh, no. No.
这是最后一站了
Afraid that's the end of the line for me,
我得绕回城镇
I'm just gonna need to loop around back to town.
没关系  我只是来兜风的
That's fine, i'm... I'm just here for the joyride.
我得走出家门
I needed to get out of the house.
呼吸新鲜的空气
Get some fresh air.
先生  你有看到那个吗?
Sir? Do you... do you see that?
你没事吧  小姐?
You all right, miss?
我没事  你有看到那架飞机吗?
Yeah. Do you see that plane?
我恐怕不知道你在说些什么
Uh, I'm afraid I'm not sure what you're talking about.
那里有一架飞机  就在…
There's a plane, right...
糟糕
Oh, no!
天啊!快停车!
Oh, my god! Stop! Stop! Stop!
那架飞机刚刚坠毁了!
That plane! It just crashed!
你确定?
Are you sure?
是的!你得开去那里  飞机刚坠毁了
Yes! Yes! You... You need to drive out there.
我可以指出方向
It just crashed. I... I can show you where it is.
开去那里?不  我不走那条路
Drive? No, uh... I don't go that way.
什么?
What?
我不走那条路
I don't go that way.
我们留在这里才安全
We need to stay here, where it's safe.
但我不能独自一人去那里
But I... I can't go out there alone.
那不是我该走的路线  我不能去
That's not my route. I can't.
要是他们需要帮忙呢?
But what if they need help?
嘿!
Hey!
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
天啊  你搞什么?
Oh, my god. What's wrong with you?
（警告）
（前方有危险材料 仅限安保人员）
有人吗?
Hello?
我需要支援  这里发生事故了
I need some help. There's been an accident.
有一架飞机坠毁…
A plane went down...
有人吗?
Hello?
我们可以放下
We can let go.
我们可以放下社会教导我们的感受
We can let go of what society has taught us to feel.
我们可以放下在平等统治下的混乱
We can let go of the chaos that reigns under the auspice of equality.
我们可以陷入我们所认知的真理
We can fall deeper into what we know is true,
那就是我们都渴望秩序
that we crave order.
让你的意识沉入这个世界  这个真理
Allow your consciousness to sink into this world, into this truth.
深陷其中  因为事情本该如此
Sink deeper into the way things are supposed to be.
爱丽丝
Alice.
♪ That I want to be your lover man ♪
♪ oh, yeah, now ♪
♪ whoo! ♪
-杰克? -你醒了
- Jack? - You're awake.
我没时间布置好餐桌
I didn't even have time to set the table.
这是怎么回事?
What's going on?
我为你准备了晚餐
Well, I'm making you dinner.
我们本应该有五道菜
Now, we were supposed to have five courses.
很不幸的  我们现在只有三道菜
Unfortunately, I think we're down to about three.
别看这个
That... don't look at that.
这道菜不能上桌
That course is officially off the menu.
发生什么事了?
What happened?
我调味的时候下手太重了
I got a little aggressive with the seasoning.
你到家多久了?
How long have you been home?
几个小时了
Uh, a few hours.
好的
Okay.
不  别看那个
Nope, don't look at that. That's...
我烹煮了烤肉
Okay, so I'm making that roast.
你在我生日时煮的那道菜
You know, the one you made for my birthday?
但我做了一点调整
Only with a few changes.
你到家时我已经回来了?
I was here when you got here?
是的  你在卧室睡觉
Yeah. Asleep in the bedroom.
烤肉需要放红萝卜吗?
Do you put carrots in a roast?
我是怎么回家的?
How did I get home?
乘坐有轨电车吧
Trolley, I think.
等等  电车司机来接我?
Wait, so he came out and got me?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
杰克  我下了车 因为我目睹了飞机坠毁
Jack, I got off the trolley. I saw a plane crash.
爱丽丝  如果真有飞机坠毁 我肯定会听到巨响
Alice, I think I would've heard if there was a plane crash.
-不  杰克  我真的看到… -坠毁时发出的巨响…
- No, Jack, I saw it... - They tend to be rather loud...
-我接着开始走向那里… -不可能会错过
- And I started walking and... - And hard to miss.
嘿  你没事吧?
Hey. Are you okay?
-不  我不知道  我没有… -怎么了?
- No, I don't know. I'm not... - What's wrong?
我做了一个很怪异的梦  真的很古怪
I had a really weird dream. A really weird dream.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你知道怪异的梦 让我感觉如何吗?
Do you know what weird dreams make me?
感觉如何?
What?
感觉肚饿
Hungry.
-你要吃红萝卜吗?  -好的
- Would you like some carrot? - Yes.
爱丽丝  我有事要对你坦诚
Alice, I want to be honest with you about something.
嗯?
Mm-hm?
我认为这个土豆泥不会成功
I don't think these mashed potatoes are gonna work.
你得先煮熟土豆  宝贝
That's because you need to boil them first, baby.
我明白了
I knew it.
我就知道少了一个步骤 我真是个白痴
I knew there was a step missing. Such an idiot.
我去烧锅吧
Let me put a pot on.
不用了
No, no, no.
-来吧  我只要… -你准备饮料吧  放轻松
-Come on, let me just put the... -Make us some drinks. Relax. Relax.
快去准备饮料
- Okay. Okay. - Make some drinks.
今晚我才是厨师!
I am your chef tonight!
嘿
- Hey. - Hm?
你爱我吗?
You love me?
我最爱你了
The most.
最爱
“快煮熟土豆  我正在煮熟土豆”
♪ Boiling the potatoes ♪ ♪ Boiling the potatoes i'm... ♪
是的  总有人从现状中受益
Yes, there are always people who will benefit from the status quo,
他们会追着我们不放
and they will come for us.
实际上  他们已经这么做了
They're already coming for us.
我愿意为了你们牺牲一切
I am willing to sacrifice everything for you.
我会付出我所拥有的一切
I will give everything I have
为所有人创造一个更美好的世界
to create this better world for all of us,
但没有你的忠诚  我就没法保护你
but I can't protect you without your loyalty.
当你承诺某事时  你信守诺言吗?
When you promise something, do you keep that promise?
你的话是你的保证吗? 是你的真理吗?
Is your word your bond? Is your word your truth?
是我们的约定吗?
Is it our covenant?
我们明天见
Until tomorrow.
♪ Why do the stars glow above? ♪
♪ Don't they know it's the end of the world? ♪
喂?
Hello?
你出到外头
You went out there.
你看到了
You saw it.
玛格丽特?
Margaret?
你看到了
You saw it.
他们在欺骗我们所有人
They're lying to all of us.
我现在不能跟你说话  玛格丽特
I can't talk to you right now, Margaret.
这里没有人发出疑问
No one asks any questions.
我们不能留在这里了  爱丽丝
We can't stay here anymore, Alice.
我没疯
I'm not crazy.
你太离谱了  你得停止这种行为
You're being ridiculous and you need to stop this.
爱丽丝  你很清楚我的为人…
Alice, you know me...
不
No.
玛格丽特?
Margaret?
不  不要!
No. No, don't!
等等!
Wait!
不  快放开我!
No! No, get off me!
玛格丽特!放开我!
Margaret! Get off me!
玛格丽特!
Margaret!
杰克  你不明白  我就在那里
Jack, you don't understand.
我目睹了整个过程
I was right there.
-我好累  爱丽丝
- I watched the whole thing. - I'm tired, Alice.
-我看着她跌下  -我想睡了
- I saw her fall. - I want to go to bed.
我尝试去帮她  但他们把我拖走
I tried to go and help, and then they dragged me away.
他们为何要把我带走?
Why would they take me away?
-你得停止!   -他们…
- You have to stop! - They...
她不可能没事的  杰克
There is no way that she's fine, Jack.
不
No.
我不知道该怎么对你说
I don't know what to tell you.
泰德此刻在医院陪她
Ted is with her at the hospital right now.
他说她需要缝几针
- He said she needs a few stitches. - Mm-mm.
她擦窗户时滑倒了  这是一场意外
She slipped cleaning the window. It was an accident.
不  我亲眼看到她  她割伤了自己
Nope. I saw her. She cut herself.
你度过了一个糟糕的夜晚
You had a bad night.
-不要!不! -你感觉不适
- Don't! No! - You weren't feeling well.
她跌倒了  你却幻想出最糟糕的情景
- She fell, and you imagined the worst case scenario. - No, don't do that.
她割破了自己的喉咙!
- She slit her throat! - That's crazy.
这太疯狂了
Crazy. It's crazy.
杰克  我亲眼看到的  她割伤了自己
Jack, I saw it happen. She cut herself open.
到处都是血  这不会只需缝几针
There was blood everywhere. It's not just a few stitches.
请不要歇斯底里
Please don't get hysterical.
杰克…
Jack...
她曾是我朋友
She was my friend.
她找我帮忙
And she came to me for help.
但我没理会她
And I ignored her.
接着发生了这种事
And then this happened.
我觉得这都是我的错
And I feel like it's my fault.
这不是任何人的错  爱丽丝 这只是一场意外
It's no one's fault, Alice. It was an accident.
不
No.
她说他们不会放过她
She said they would come after her
因为她知道一些事情
because she knew something.
他们为何对发生的事撒谎?
Why are they lying about what happened?
-拜托  请你停止吧  他们究竟在隐藏什么?
- Please, just stop. - What are they hiding?
宝贝  你得承认这一切都很怪异
Come on, baby, you have to admit this is weird.
-停止!  -这很不对劲!
- Stop! - There's something off!
你在胜利项目负责什么?
What are you doing at the victory project?
你知道我的工作  爱丽丝 我是一名技术工程师
You know what I do, Alice. I'm a technical engineer.
我知道
I know.
但他们在做些什么?
But what are they doing?
拜托…
Please...
究竟发生了什么?
What's actually happening?
别问我
Don't ask me that.
开发先进材料?
The development of progressive materials?
-这甚至是什么意思?  -你知道我们不能谈论这件事
- What does that even mean? - You know we can't talk about this.
-这啥意思?  -不能谈论这件事
拜托  这是什么意思?
Come on, what does it mean?
这到底意味着什么?你知道吗?
What does it even mean? Do you know?
你知道法兰克实际上在做什么吗?
Do you even know what frank is actually doing?
这是机密
It's classified.
我们甚至不被允许
We're not even allowed to discuss our jobs
与其他部门讨论工作内容 你是知道的
with other departments, you know that.
要是玛格丽特是对的呢?
What if Margaret was right?
停止吧  爱丽丝
Stop it, Alice.
要是这地方很危险呢?
What if this place is dangerous?
-够了!
- What if... - Stop it!
我是这个重要项目的一份子  爱丽丝
I'm part of something important, Alice.
法兰克想完成的使命意义非凡
This mission, what frank's doing, it matters.
我知道  宝贝  但你没在听我说
I know that, baby, but you're not listening to me.
不是每个人都能获得这个机会
No! Not everyone gets this opportunity.
你要是一直这样说话
And if you keep talking like this,
会让我们失去一切的
you're gonna put it all at risk.
你担心被降职?
You're worried about a demotion?
你只担心这件事?
That's what you're worried about?
还有我们的人生
Our life...
爱丽丝  我们共同打造的人生
Alice. Our life together.
这一切
This.
我们有可能会失去这一切
We could lose this.
求求你
Please.
冷静下来
Just get a hold of yourself.
拜托
Please.
该死的
Fuck's sake.
胜利社区是安全可靠的
Victory is safe and secure.
是你梦寐以求  养家糊口的好地方
A perfect place to raise the family you've always wanted,
跟朋友一起放松 景
when you're not relaxing with friends
享受这令人叹为观止的风
or enjoying the breathtaking scenery
这个阳光普照的天堂
of this sunbaked paradise.
虽然你可能会发现 俱乐部泳池才是最佳美景
Although, you might find the best scenery at the club pool.
在这里  你可以过上你应得的生活
Here you can live the life you deserve.
我们都可以过这样的生活…
We can all live the life...
如果我能对法兰克说些什么
If I could tell frank anything,
我会对他说“谢谢你”
it would just be, "thank you." Because I didn't know
我不知道我原来可以这么快乐
I could be this happy.
老实说  我甚至不记得 在胜利社区之前的生活
Honestly, I don't even remember my life before victory.
法兰克给予我们 难能可贵的机会  我不会…
Frank gave us the opportunity of a lifetime. I wouldn't...
我们能在这里实在太幸运了
We are so lucky to be here.
-最近有流行病吗? -不  我没听说过
- Is there a bug going around? - No, not that I know of.
我想你只是操劳过度
Think this is just run-of-the-mill exhaustion.
最近出现了什么新的烦恼事吗?
You had any new stresses or pressures lately?
她目睹泰德的妻子跌下
- Um... - -She saw Ted's wife fall.
我想她也许是惊吓过度
Thought maybe it might be shock.
天啊  她摔得不轻
Boy, that was quite a tumble.
肯定感到很尴尬
She was so embarrassed.
她没有摔倒
It... it wasn't a tumble.
她割破了自己的喉咙
She slit her throat.
-爱丽丝 -不是的
- Alice. - Uh, no, no, no.
目睹创伤经过往往会导致记忆扭曲
Witnessing a trauma can often lead to distorted memories.
甚至引发噩梦
Even nightmares.
这…
It's...
我可以给你开一些药
I have some pills I can prescribe for that.
我想我不需要
Uh, I... I really don't think that I need those.
（玛格丽特沃特金斯 危险分子）作为预防
Oh, they're precautionary.
我大多数病人服用后都有见效
Most of my patients have had quite a bit of success with them.
这会让你放轻松
They will just keep you relaxed.
她不需要这些药
She doesn't need those.
这没什么问题
This isn't a problem.
我们可以自己处理
We can handle it ourselves.
好的  我会记录在档案上
Well, I'll just keep that on file.
你对玛格丽特做了什么?
What did you do to Margaret?
你说什么?
Pardon?
泰德的妻子
Ted's wife.
抱歉  我…
I'm sorry, I'm just... I...
我还是不明白她怎么会没事
I still don't understand how she's okay.
你也不想我拿你的病情
You wouldn't want me discussing the details of your treatment
跟其他病人讨论  对吧?
with my other patients, now, would you?
我不介意
Mm... I wouldn't mind.
我真的很想知道你治疗她的细节
I would just... I would really love to know the details of...Of how you fixed her.
如你所知  我们这里 同时提供精神和身体护理
Well, as you know, we provide both psychiatric and physical care here.
而玛格丽特两者都需要
And Margaret was in need of both.
好消息是  她的身体没什么大碍
The good news is, is that physically, she's fine,
但她精神上出了问题
but psychologically, she wasn't.
她出现了严重的负面情绪
She was having significant troubles.
导致情绪爆发也有妄想症
Outbursts. Paranoia.
她让泰德无法完成工作
She made it impossible for Ted to do his job,
所以他不再为胜利项目工作
so he no longer works for the victory project.
她需要相当多的帮助
She needed quite a bit of help.
不像你
Ah... not like you.
不
No.
我们没这个必要
It's not necessary here.
这是完全不同的状况
It's a totally different scenario.
你们英国人都是这么说的吗?
What is it that you brits say?
“保持冷静  坚持不懈”
Ah! "Keep calm and carry on."
杰克  你送我出去吧?
Jack. Walk me out?
当然
Of course.
记得…
And remember...
-有什么事就打给我 -谢谢你
- That I'm always a phone call away. - Oh, thank you.
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
哦  快啊
Oh, come on.
你知道我们在这方面的立场
You know our position on that.
很高兴你回来了  你落下了这个
So glad you came back. You left this.
我真是健忘
I'd forget my head if it wasn't screwed on.
杰克  你该回去工作了吧?
Jack, shouldn't you be getting back to work?
是的
Yeah. Of course.
晚上见
- See you tonight. - Mm-hm.
好的
Okay.
不  不是…
Oh, no. No. It's not...
（体检文档）
（案例摘要：档案人拒绝接受治疗 已发出最后警告）
♪ I used to play around with hearts... ♪
我也许会邀请雪莉共舞
Might ask shelley to dance at some point,
如果感觉时机对了
if it feels like a good time.
你还在洗澡?我们快迟到了
You're still in the bath? We're gonna be late.
有看到我替你准备的裙子吗?
You see the dress I got you?
那是我上个星期挑选的
Picked it out last week.
我无法停止想象你穿上的画面
I couldn't stop picturing you in it.
-谢谢 -好的
- Thank you. - Yeah.
你看上去美丽极了
You look incredible.
我在想我们或许该尝试不同的事
Been thinking we should try something kind of crazy.
♪ She'd hold me close and kiss me ♪
我们生个孩子吧
Let's have a baby.
♪ Poor little fool ♪
-什么?  -不是现阶段
- What? - Not right now.
我很爱你
Look, I love you.
想要与你拥有更多
And I want more of you.
我想有个迷你版的你
And I think I want a little you.
我也不知道  但这感觉会很有趣
I don't know, I think it would be fun.
好好想一想吧?
Just think about it, okay?
好的
Okay.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I was a fool... ♪
今晚一定会很棒  你会美艳动人
Tonight's gonna be great. You're gonna look beautiful.
♪ The next day she was gone ♪
♪ and I knew she'd lied to me ♪
♪ she left me with a broken heart ♪
♪ and won her victory ♪
晚上好  我们一直在等你（今天获得胜利 明天统治世界）
Good evening. We've been waiting for you.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
你们的座位是全场最好的
You have the best table in the house.
-见到你真好 -嘿  各位
- Good to see you, man. - Hey, guys.
你们俩怎么总在争吵?你怎么了?
Why are you two always fighting? What's wrong with you?
-总是如此 -我们没事
- Always. Constantly. - We're fine. We're fine.
-嗨 -你总算到了!嗨
- Hi. - Oh! Finally! Hi.
你好  天啊!
Hello. Oh, my god!
快  来一杯
Here, drink this.
你看上去像个洋娃娃
You look just like a little doll.
快旋转吧!
Spin, spin, spin! Ah!
这是我的  这是你的  干下去
This is me. This is you. Here, go, go, go.
-一饮而尽  就是这样! -一口干下去!
- All the way back. - Just drink it all!
就是这样才对!
- There we go. - There we go!
闹事者全到齐了
Here are the troublemakers.
真不敢相信我们被允许 把你们放在同一桌
I can't believe we're allowed to put all of you at one table.
老实说  出于保险考量 这样的安排更为恰当
I think it's better for insurance purposes,
这倒是真的
- to be honest. - That is true.
爱丽丝  你感觉如何?
Alice, how are you feeling?
我很好
I'm... I'm well. I'm doing well.
这里好漂亮
This is beautiful.
谢谢你邀请我们
Thank you so much for inviting us.
如果我听到玻璃破碎的声音 我会立马转身回来
And if I hear glass breaking, I'm coming right back here.
哦  不要诱惑我们
Oh, don't tempt us
不然我们整晚都在打碎玻璃
or we'll be breaking glass all night.
我们待会儿舞池见?
See you on the dance floor later?
是的  夫人  当然
Yes, ma'am. Of course.
我丈夫真懂得如何举办派对  对吧?
Can my husband throw a party or what?
他为我们做了很多
He does so much for us.
已超出我们所能偿还的
More than we could ever repay.
但我还是想赠他一份小礼物
But I have attempted a little... gift for him.
这也献给我们所有人
- Uh-oh. - -For all of us, really.
希望大家喜欢
I hope you enjoy.
来吧!
Let's go!
你出到外头
You went out there.
你看到了
You saw it.
她情绪爆发
She was having outbursts.
也有妄想症
Paranoia.
很不赖吧?
How 'bout that?
原来你在这里  我向你鞠躬
There you are. I bow to you.
快鼓掌!快啊!
Now, make some noise! Come on!
你喜欢吗?
You like that?
大家喜欢吗?
Did you guys like that?
快站起来  表示感谢!
Get off of your seats, come on!
你好吗  亲爱的?看到你真好
How are you, sweetheart? Good to see you.
这就是我提到过的
All right, this is what I'm talking about.
努力工作  卖力玩乐
You work hard, you play hard.
你怎么看  杰克?
What do you say, Jacko?
-杰克  我想回家 -什么?
- Jack, I want to go home. - What?
我想回家
I want to go.
来吧  提姆!
Come on, Tim! Come on, Tim!
好的!
All right!
喔
Whoo!
怎么了?快鼓掌
How about that? Put your hands together.
求求你  我们得离开
Please, we need to leave.
现在就离开
We need to leave right now. Please.
我们给你倒一杯酒
- We'll just pour you a drink. - Please.
没事的
- No. - You'll be okay.
最好的都献给胜利社区!天啊!
Only the best for victory. My goodness!
好的  大家请坐吧
All right, take a seat.
我现在有负担了 如果试图跟着这么做
Uh, I have the burden now of trying to follow that,
这会很难  但是…
which will be hard, but...
-  杰克…-我得承认
- Jack... - I have to admit that I, uh...
我打算…
I was planning...
我也打算来段小展示…
A little presentation of my own.
我知道
I know.
我明白 好的
I know. Yeah. All right. All right.
杰克钱伯斯
Jack chambers.
请你上台来
If I could have you up here for a minute.
杰克
Jack.
杰克 拜托  我得回家 我们必须离开这里
Jack, please, I need to go home. We need to leave.
来吧  各位  给他来点掌声
Come on, everybody, give him a round of applause.
他需要一点鼓励
Needs a little encouragement.
热烈鼓掌
Big round of applause.
我们给他一个 盛大的胜利式欢迎!
Let's give him a big victory welcome!
杰克钱伯斯
Jack chambers.
今晚是我一年中最喜欢的夜晚
Tonight is my favorite night of the year.
我很喜欢看到大家聚集一起
I love seeing everybody under one roof,
看看我们都成长了多少
seeing how much we've all grown.
但是没几个人…
But few...
没几个人…
Few have grown as...
能像这位年轻人一样
Impressively...
成长的如此优秀
As this young man right here.
天知道我为此争论了很久
I've debated long and hard about this, lord knows. Whew!
这确实很不寻常
It's certainly out of the ordinary.
但你们知道吗?这个人不一般
But you know what? This man is out of the ordinary.
这人让我敬而远之
This man, I am in awe of.
杰克钱伯斯  我很荣幸…
Jack chambers, I am honored...
邀请你加入…
To invite you to join our...
我们的高级顾问委员会
Senior advisory board.
你真是你自称的那个人吗?
Are you the man that you say you are?
这很符合我们的要求
It's a good fit.
谢谢你的忠诚
Thank you for your loyalty.
有更多美好的事物即将到来
More good things to come.
你们怎么看  女士先生们
How 'bout that, ladies and gentlemen.
你们想看这小子跳舞吗?
You wanna see the boy dance?
看看这小子的舞步!
Look at this boy dance!
来吧!
Come on! Come on!
看看他的厉害!
Look what he can do!
-别这样说  你会找到另一份工作的  -爱丽丝!
- Don't say that. You're gonna get another job. - Alice!
嘿  怎么了?亲爱的
Hey. What's wrong? Honey.
发生什么事了?怎么了?
What happened? What's wrong?
这太棒了!
It's extraordinary!
一切都安好  没事的
Everything's fine. It's okay.
邦妮  我们得离开这里
Bunny, we need to go.
立刻就走
We need to get out of here right now.
-不  我们没事的  -我们必须离开
- No, no, no. We're okay. - We need to go.
告诉我吧  发生什么事了?
We're okay. Come on. Tell me, what happened?
怎么样?
How about that, huh?
你们在看他跳舞吗?
You watching him dance?
玛格丽特说得对
Margaret was right.
她问了他们不想我们问的问题
She was asking questions that they don't want us to ask.
他们于是把她灭口
And so they silenced her.
她没有滑倒  那不是一场意外
She didn't slip. It wasn't an accident.
我亲眼目睹过程  我看到她跌下
I saw it happen. I saw her fall.
他们对一切撒了谎
They're lying about everything.
跳舞吧  杰克!
Dance, Jack!
我们让他旋转  好吗?
Let's make him spin, shall we?
我到外头去  我看到了
And so I went out there, and I saw it.
你到哪去了?
You went... you went out where?
没错  就是这样!加速  小子!
Yeah, that's it! Come on, boy, faster!
继续!快啊!
Keep it going! Come on! Come on! Yeah!
就是这样!
That's it!
这让大家确信吧?
Doesn't that make you believe?
站起来!
Stand up!
站起来  鞠躬!这是你应得的!
Stand up, take a bow! Take a bow, you deserve it!
当我触摸它时  我看到了一些东西
And when I touched it, I saw something.
我想起了更多事
And I keep remembering more.
我听到了法兰克的声音 他进入了我的脑海…
And I heard frank's voice, and he's in my head...
这不仅仅是庆祝我们从社会的
It's more than just a celebration
任意规则中解放出来
of our freedom from society's arbitrary regulations,
这也是对潜能释放的庆祝!
it's a celebration of potential unleashed!
提醒着我们是谁!
It's a reminder of who we are!
我带你去看吧?我们到外头去
Can I just show you? Let's just go out there.
大家的注意力此刻被分散了
Everybody will be distracted right now.
我们可以开迪恩的车
We can take Dean's car.
-我们可以前往… -停止!
- We can head to... - Stop. Stop. Stop it!
-你疯了吗? -什么?
- Have you lost your mind? - What?
你去了总部?
You went to headquarters?
-我以为有飞机坠毁
- Because I thought I saw a plane crash. - It is the one rule...
这是他们要求我们遵守的首要规矩
- No, I know... - They ask us to respect.
你知道这有多危险
You know how dangerous it is.
我们不会倒退
We are not going backwards.
反而正在向前推进  对吗?
We're pushing forwards, yes?
我们正往前走!
We move!
-你偷走了科林斯医生的东西? -因为玛格丽特不可能没事!
- You stole from Dr. Collins? - Because Margaret can't be okay!
控制住自己  爱丽丝!
Get a hold of yourself, Alice!
你现在的表现很幼稚
You are behaving like a child.
你丈夫此刻正度过
Your husband is out there
他生命中最重要的夜晚
having the most important night of his life.
大家都在为他欢庆
He's being celebrated,
而你却在这里试图破坏?
and you're in here trying to ruin it?
不是的!
No! No!
你听起来跟玛格丽特一模一样!
You sound exactly like Margaret!
这是谁的世界?
Whose world is it?
我们的!
Ours!
这是谁的世界?
Whose world is this?
我们的!
Ours!
-这是谁的世界? -我们的!
- Whose world is this? - Ours!
这是谁的世界?
Whose world is this?
我们的!
Ours!
-这是谁的世界?我们的! -我们的!
- Whose world is it? Ours! - Ours!
这是谁的世界?
Whose world is it?
我们的
- Ours! - Ours!
-这是谁的世界?我们的! -我们的!
- Whose world is it? Ours! - Ours!
他们称之为提取操作
They're calling it operation extract.
这需要更高层的权限
It's higher security clearance.
我将全权负责整个企划
I'm gonna be heading the whole thing myself,
这说明了法兰克对我的信任
which is a real vote of confidence from frank, I think.
♪ See the pyramids ♪
♪ along the nile ♪
-欢迎! -欢迎你们!
- Welcome! - Welcome!
他在这里
There he is.
天啊  这真漂亮  进来吧
Oh, my. Those are beautiful. Come on in.
请进
Come on in.
我为你挑选的  谢谢
I want it for you. Thank you.
我们迟到了吗?我感觉来迟了
Are we late? I feel like we're late.
我们简直是同时抵达
We literally are arriving at the same time.
这些盘子装的是什么?哇!
What are these platters? Wow!
无论这些是什么  我都好喜欢
Whatever's going on here, I love. I love.
你喜欢吗?
You like it?
我很高兴  比尔
- Yeah, the decor is... - I'm glad, bill. I'm glad.
兄弟  快说实话
All right, buddy, tell me the truth.
他真的会来?
Is he really coming?
这是给你的  我想他会出现的
This is for you. I think he's coming.
你是怎么让法兰克同意来你家的?
How the hell did you get frank to come to your house?
不是我  是爱丽丝的功劳
It wasn't me. It was Alice.
哦  这些都是福利  我明白了 这就是你现在的生活方式
These are the perks. I get it. This is how you're living.
这房子的一切装潢都来自家具目录?
Is everything in this house from the catalogue?
不愧是一所房子  快给我看看戒指
It's a house. Show me the ring. Let me see it.
我们有比邦妮早到吗?
Did we beat bunny?
她不会来了
Uh, she... she's not coming.
我就说过了
- Hm. - Told you.
抱歉  男孩们  让一让…
- Sorry, boys. Can I just get... - Yeah, yeah.
你会跳舞是件好事
You know, it's a good thing you can dance,
因为你长得十分没有吸引力
'cause you're so hideously unattractive.
-他们来了! -你到底藏了多少秘密…
- They're here! - How many secrets do you...
谢谢
Thank you.
见到你真好
- It's good to see you. - Wow.
我就知道  我告诉佩吉 这肯定是无需打领带的休闲场合
I knew it. I told peg. It's gonna be a no-tie event.
杰克!你这疯狂的王八蛋!
- Frank. - Jack! You crazy son of a bitch!
你要我怎么处理这个?
What do you want me to do with this?
坚持住
Hold on to it.
我对她说这会是个休闲场合
I told her it was gonna be like a casual thing.
-请加冰块   - 喔
- Put that on ice. - Wow.
-谢谢你能来    -我很为你感到骄傲
- Thanks for coming. - I'm proud of you.
-感谢    -顺道一提  这所房子漂亮极了
- Thank you. - What a lovely home, by the way.
你能替雪莉调一杯鸡尾酒吗?
Jack, could you make shelley a cocktail?
当然可以
Of course.
嘿  法兰克  昨晚的派对真是太棒了
Hey, frank, that was a hell of a party last night.
确实如此
It was.
我也试图让妻子喝一杯马提尼
I'm trying to get my wife into a Martini glass.
-他喜欢我说的笑话 -才没有
- He liked that. - No, he didn't.
-你的酒呢? -就在这里  干杯!
- Where's your drink? - It's right here. Cheers!
干杯  这是一个很美妙的家
Cheers. It's a wonderful home.
-你好吗? -我吗?
- How are you? - Me?
我好极了
- I'm amazing. - Mm-hm.
我很高兴杰克度过了昨晚的美好夜晚
After the night Jack had, I'm incredible.
是的  当然
Right. Of course.
干杯  谢谢你能来
Cheers. Thanks for coming.
你昨晚是个赢家
- You were a triumph last night. - Oh!
我们还没停止谈论你
We haven't stopped talking about you.
你们尽情享受吧
You guys go now and enjoy yourselves.
我要去清洗盘子  待会儿见
I'm gonna go back to the plates and finish up,
-我能帮忙吗?
- and, um, I'll see you in... - Can I help you?
-不用  -你确定?
- No, no, no, no, go. - You sure? Okay.
去聊八卦吧
Promise. Go snoop.
我很喜欢这个唱机
I love this record player.
是吗?你喜欢这个  比尔?
- You do? You like it, bill? - I love it.
我家里有一个长凳  你是如何…
At my house, I have a bench. How did you get...
你现在知道了
You can probably tell by now
开胃菜才是 我真正表达自己和打破常规的地方
that appetizers are where I really express myself and buck convention.
这是一门手艺
It's a skill.
你有空时可以教教我
Maybe you can teach me sometime.
这是学不来的
Can't be taught.
我得知一件非常令人兴奋的事
I learned something very exciting.
是吗?是什么事?
Oh, really? What's that?
听说你和杰克想生孩子
Rumor is you and Jack are trying.
哦  这个嘛…
Oh, well...
我们再看看吧
- We'll see. - Mm.
希望能看到一个小男孩
Hope we'll see a little boy.
很抱歉邦妮没听信你说的
I'm sorry bunny didn't believe you.
但你也同样没相信玛格丽特
But then again, you didn't believe Margaret, so...
大家凭什么要相信你呢?
Why should anyone believe you?
天啊  你真让我着迷
My god, you fascinate me.
我一直在等待像你这样的人出现
Because I've been waiting for someone like you.
一个来挑战我的人
Someone to challenge me.
所有伟人都是被逼到极限
No great man has changed the course of history
才能改变历史的进程
without being pushed to the limits of his potential.
而你就是那个逼我爆发潜能的人
And you push me.
是的
Yeah.
我希望你能继续这么做
I do hope you keep going.
但你却躲在这里
And yet, here you are.
忙着准备晚餐
Preparing dinner.
像个乖乖女
Like a good girl.
-坐下吧 -好的
- Sit. - Absolutely.
你知道是男孩还是女孩吗?
Do you know if it's a boy or a girl?
不  但我希望是个男孩  谢谢
No, I hope it's a boy. Thank you.
男孩总是令人喜爱  对吧?
- Can't get enough of 'em, right?
女孩很难管教
Girls are hard. They are.
-我去一下那里   -谢谢
- I'll be right there, all right? - Thank you.
爱丽丝告诉我你是个很棒的网球手
You know, Alice tells me you're a hell of a tennis player.
-她这么说过吗? -是这样吗?
- Oh, she does? - Is that right? Yeah.
她只是出于礼貌
She's being polite.
我们正在寻找激烈的竞争对手
Well, we're looking for some fierce competitors.
你哪天准备好加入就打给我
If you're ever ready to get out there, call me.
我听说过你的反手击球技巧 这是家喻户晓的事
I've heard about that backhand, though, it's famous.
如果你想找拍档  欢迎随时找我
If you want a partner, I'm yours, man.
那很有压力  我不知道…
That's a lot of pressure. I don't know if...
谢谢
Thank you.
我吃鱼  不知道你们想吃什么
I'm having the fish. I don't know what you guys are having.
很高兴看到熟悉的事物
Nice to see a familiar face.
总而言之  那里的窗口装有板条?
Um, so anyways, those windows right there, the slatted windows?
那实际上被称为“百叶窗”窗户
They're actually called "jalousie" windows.
你知道吗?
Did you know that?
-你并不知道 -天啊
- You didn't know why. - Oh, boy.
词源是“嫉妒”
So, the etymology is... "Jealousy."
当你说“这是谁的宝宝?”
And you say, "whose baby is this?"
他们回答“这是你的宝宝”
And they say, "it's your baby."
你接着说“这怎么可能?”
And you say, "how could that be?"
但那确实是你的宝宝
And it is your baby.
我每年都这样做
And I just do it every year.
维丽特  你是哪里人?
Violet, where are you from?
-你说什么? -我说“你是哪里人?”
- Pardon? - I said, "where are you from?"
费城
Philadelphia.
-我来自费城!   -你是说真的?
- Mm! I'm from Philadelphia! - Are you serious?
-我并不知道  -我就知道我喜欢你是有原因的
- I didn't know that. - I knew I liked you.
这里大多数女性都来自费城
Most of the women here are from Philadelphia.
或巴尔的摩和芝加哥
Or Baltimore. Or Chicago.
我有注意到
I've noticed.
你们要喝点什么吗?
Mm. Can I get anyone anything?
我绝对不想念那里的冬天
I for one do not miss the winters.
不  我在阳光下才能茁壮成长
No, no, no. I thrive in the sunshine,
即使我有着雪花石膏色的皮肤
even though I'm alabaster-skinned.
我很喜欢阳光  也喜欢海滩
I love the sunshine. I love the beach.
她确实喜欢
- Mm. - She does.
你最后去过哪个海滩?
What was the last beach you went to?
我读过关于海滩的有趣事实
Oh, fun fact about the beach.
-是什么?
- I read this. - Yeah?
海滩实际上是全世界最脏的地方
Beaches are actually some of the filthiest places in the whole world.
-是个充满疾病的沙盒  还有…   -彼得!
- Just a sandbox of disease and... - Peter!
请不要在饭桌上提到“疾病”
Do not say "disease" at the dinner table.
这是事实  有必要让他们知道
It's true. They need to know.
我大概能猜到  希尔顿黑德? 科德角?
I can probably guess. Hilton head? Cape Cod?
还是泽西海岸?
Or the Jersey shore?
我们都在海岛度蜜月
And we all honeymooned in sea island,
或波科诺斯  或尼亚加拉大瀑布
or the poconos, or Niagara Falls.
我想这些都是很受欢迎的 蜜月目的地
I think those are popular honeymoon destinations.
-也非常昂贵  -漂亮极了
- Expensive. - Mm-hm. Beautiful, beautiful.
彼得  你的故事还没说完
Peter, you, uh... you haven't finished your story.
比尔或许是我见过…
Mm! Bill over here's probably
-最差劲的高尔夫球手之一 -抱歉  彼得
- one of the worst golf players... - I'm sorry, Peter.
我还没说完 维丽特  你是在哪认识比尔的?
I'm not quite finished. Violet, where did you meet bill?
我们是在火车上相识的
Well, we met on a train.
-前往波斯顿 -前往波斯顿
- To Boston. - To Boston.
是的
Yeah.
对
Yes.
你的车票掉了
You dropped your ticket.
他弯下腰捡起 交给了你  对吧?
And he bent down, picked it up, gave it to you, right?
确实是这样
It is, yeah.
玛格丽特也是这样认识泰德的
That's how Margaret met Ted.
佩吉  黛比麦金太尔好像
And peg, am I right in thinking
也是这样认识她丈夫的  对吧?
that's how Debbie mcintyre met her husband?
是的  他们是这样相遇的
Yes, I am. That's how they met.
-没错  我真嫉妒 -是吗?
- Yes, that's true. I'm jealous. - Is it?
说真的  这真是个甜美的故事
- Honestly, it's such a sweet story. - -Wow.
对
Yeah. Yeah.
很有意思吧  这些巧合…
Isn't that funny, the way those coincidences...
太不可思议了
Incredible.
我们被告知的不同故事只有这么几个
There are only so many different stories we're told.
我们只被告知该记得些什么
We're told what we remember.
直到…
Until...
我们试图回忆起…
We try to remember things...
他们想要我们忘记的事
That they want us to forget.
-就像玛格丽特 -爱丽丝…
- Like Margaret. - Alice...
不  杰克  没关系
No. Jack. It's okay.
我很想听听看她想说些什么
I'm curious to hear where she's going with this.
法兰克正在对我们做某些事
Frank is doing something to us.
让我们产生妄想症 出现记忆问题  也变得歇斯底里
Delusions, memory problems, hysteria.
我们在玛格丽特身上看过这些症状
We saw these issues with Margaret,
并且知道这是完全可以治愈的
and know that it's, uh, completely curable.
科林斯医生给你开了一整套处方药
Dr. Collins prescribed you a suite of medications,
但你很显然没在服用
which you are clearly not taking.
我们应该问的是为什么…
The question is why...
他在骗我们  他欺骗了我们所有人
He's lying to us. He's lying to all of us.
你最好的朋友邦妮  非常担心你
Bunny, your best friend, is worried about you.
她认为你需要协助
She thinks that you need help.
这是她今晚没来的原因吗?
Is that why she's not here tonight?
因为你不想被提醒这件事
Because you didn't want to be reminded of that.
他在利用你  他利用了我们所有人
He's using you. He's using all of us.
你们甚至知道胜利项目是什么吗?
Do you even know what the victory project actually is?
-你有问过吗? -你有吗?
- Have you ever asked? - Do you?
这就是你去到外头的原因?
Is that why you went out there?
你去了总部?
To headquarters?
什么?
What?
我很抱歉
- I'm sorry. I'm so sorry. - Alice...
但你不知道他做了什么
But you don't know what he's doing.
你擅自外出
You wandered out by yourself.
无视每一条规则
You ignored every rule.
她把你们的生命置于危险之中
And she put all your lives in danger.
是的  我确实外出
Yes, I did go out there
也去过总部  看到了他隐藏的东西
and I went to headquarters and I saw what he's hiding.
-我隐藏的东西 -他欺骗了大家
- What I'm hiding. - He's lying to us.
他向我们所有人撒谎
- Oh, dear. - -He's lying to all of us
胜利项目实际上的目的
about what the victory project actually is.
他把我们都困在这里
- He's trapped us here. - Alice...
困在这里?
Trapped?
我希望没人感觉到受困 你们感觉被困住了?
I hope no one feels trapped. Do you feel trapped?
维丽特?
Violet?
佩吉?
Peg?
这是你的精神病引起的猜疑
This is your psychosis.
你把信任视为一种被困的感觉
You are experiencing trust as a feeling of entrapment,
然而你每天都付出信任
yet you trust every day.
大家都一样
We all do.
你今晚邀请 我们来你家是出于信任
Tonight, you've trusted us in your home.
犹如我信任你踏入我的卧室
Just like I trusted you in my bedroom.
爱丽丝
Alice?
你还记得那件事吗?
Do you remember that?
他试图创造一个世界
He's... he's trying to create a world.
-如果你想表达自己的论点  -他利用了我们
- If you want to articulate your own argument... - He's using us.
-试着用你自己的话来说  爱丽丝 -他在利用我们每一个人
- Try using your own words, Alice. - He's using all of us.
-用你自己的话! -这食物里有什么?
- In your own words! - What's in this food?
我们来谈谈这个!
Let's talk about that!
-这些食物来自哪? -哦  我很抱歉  各位
- Where did it come from? Huh? - Oh, I'm sorry, everyone.
-抱歉  -让我们想一想
- I'm sorry. - Let's just think about it.
-我很抱歉   -胜利社区的牛奶
- I'm sorry, Violet. - Victory milk.
-这是一个反常现象  -胜利社区的肉类、鸡蛋
- This is... this is an anomaly. - Victory meat. Victory eggs.
-这全都来自于他 -通常不会有这种事发生的
- It doesn't usually happen. - It all comes from him.
她病得很重
She's very sick
-她会得到所需的帮助
- and she will get the help that she needs... - Everything we're told...
-我答应你们两人 -我们的一切都来自他!
- I promise you both. - Everything we are given comes from him!
这关系到控制力
And it's all about control.
这才是关键
It's all about control.
我们根本不知道… 他也许在食物里下毒!
We wouldn't even... He might be poisoning the food!
够了!
Enough!
我们来到你家
We come to your house,
坐在你的餐桌前
we sit at your table,
你却侮辱和贬低我丈夫?
and you insult and degrade my husband?
他邀你加入与他一样非凡的重要项目
He invites you to be a part of something as extraordinary as he is,
你却像个被宠坏的孩子
and you sit there like a spoiled brat,
一直为自己幻想出的问题要求解答
demanding answers to questions you've made up.
这其中有一个模式  对吧?
There's a pattern, isn't there?
一个自私  娇生惯养的抱怨模式
A pattern of selfish, pampered whining.
或只是你渴望得到刺激感?
Or is it just a desperation to be exciting?
嗯
Hm?
拼命抵抗这个难得可贵的机会
Spitting in the face of this opportunity.
这十分可悲  你绝望的妄想症
It's heartbreaking that your sad, desperate paranoia
能破坏我们正在尝试构建的东西
could destroy what we're trying to build.
我不愿再听你可悲的咆哮
Well, I won't listen to your pathetic ranting any longer.
法兰克  亲爱的
Frank, honey?
我会在车上等
I'll be in the car.
看来…
Well...
杰克  我想你妻子喝多了
Jack, I think you may have overserved your wife.
谢谢
Thank you.
我对你有着更高的期待
I was expecting so much more from you.
祝你好运  爱丽丝
Good luck, Alice.
杰克  我们谈一谈
Jack, let's talk.
你今晚过得尽兴吗?
Did you enjoy yourself tonight?
什么?
What?
不  我今晚一点也不开心
No, I didn't enjoy myself tonight.
你策划一整晚想要破坏我
You planned a whole evening to sabotage me.
不!我绝不会这样对你
No! No, I would never do that to you.
我绝不会这样对你  我爱你
I would never do that to you. I love you.
我只是试图拯救我们
I'm trying... I'm trying to save us.
你去到外头  是为了拯救我们
You're trying to save us by going out there.
是的  我看到飞机坠毁  我告诉你了
Yes, because I saw a plane crash. I told you.
杰克  我在餐桌上说的都是真的
But, Jack, everything I said at that table is true.
法兰克亲口对我承认
Frank even admitted it to me.
他在厨房里对我说了
He admitted it to me in the kitchen.
我才会做出那样的行为 接着发生了后面那些事
That's why I did that. That's why all of that happened.
他不可能这么做的
He wouldn't have done that.
杰克…
Jack...
大家都把我当成疯子
Everyone is acting like I'm crazy.
但我没疯
And I'm not crazy.
我需要你听我说
And I need you to listen to me.
I need you to listen to me.
嘿
Hey.
嘿  看着我
Hey. Hey, look at me. Look at me. Look at me.
对我来说…
To me...
你…
You are...
你比这一切都重要
You are bigger than all of this.
你比胜利社区更重要
You are bigger than victory.
你比法兰克更重要
You are bigger than frank.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我不相信他
I don't believe in him.
我一点也不信任他
And I don't trust him.
我也不信任这地方
And I don't trust this place.
我不想留在这里了
And I don't want to be here anymore.
我不想留下
I don't want to be here anymore.
我们必须离开
And we need to leave.
我们离开这里  到哪都行
We need to leave. And we can go anywhere.
我们可以去任何地方 创造属于自己的世界
We can go anywhere and we can create our own world,
那里只有你和我  我们不会有事的
and it will be you and me and we'll be okay.
我们去哪都不重要 重要的是我们能在一起
And it's not about where we go, it's just that we're together.
求求你?
Please? Please? Please?
Please?
求你了
Please.
好的
Okay.
好吗?
Okay?
好的
Okay.
好吗?
Okay?
好的
Okay.
我爱你
I love you. I love you.
但我们今晚就得离开
But we need to go tonight.
我们不能留在这里了
We need to go. We can't be here.
嘿
Hey. Hey.
我爱你  我们走吧
I love you. Let's go.
我爱你
I love you.
-好  -好的
- Okay. - 'Kay. Okay.
杰克?
Jack?
我准备了吃的 以免我们得彻夜开车
I packed us a snack in case we drive all night long,
我把一切都收拾好了
but I think I packed everything.
我们走吧
Let's go.
宝贝  走吧
Baby, let's go. Come on.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
什么?
What?
我很爱你  爱丽丝
I love you so much, Alice.
宝贝  怎么了?
Baby, what's wrong?
我很努力避免这种事发生
I tried so hard to keep this from happening.
-什么?我们… -请你相信我…
- What? Let's... - Please believe...
宝贝  我们得立刻走
Baby, we need to go. We need to go.
你得开车 我们得离开  快开车
Baby, you need to drive. We need to go. Go. Whoa.
-我很抱歉 -不!
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry. - No. No! No!
不  杰克!求求你 我可以变得更好!
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Alice. -No, Jack, please! I can be better!
-我可以变得更好! 很抱歉!  -爱丽丝  我很抱歉!
- I can be better! I'm so sorry! - Alice, I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
我能变得更好  求求你  宝贝!
- Let me be better, please! - I'm sorry!
我能变得更好
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry! - Baby, please!
- Let me be better. - I'm sorry!
-放开我!  -抱歉
- Get off me! - I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
让我变得更好
- Let me be better! - I'm sorry.
杰克  求求你!
- I'm so... - Jack, please!
他们弄疼我了!不!
They're hurting me! No! No!
不!杰克  他们弄疼我了!
No! Jack! They're hurting me!
他们弄疼我了!
They're hurting me!
靠!
Fuck!
不  求求你  不要…
No, please, please. Please, don't...
♪ Darlin' I ♪
“亲爱的”
♪ with you all the time ♪
“我要一直陪着你”
♪ can't you see ♪
“你难道看不出”
♪ I long to be ♪
“我渴望…”
我要怎么照顾好你?
How am I gonna take care of you?
别这么说
Don't say that.
你会找到 另一份工作的  没事的
You're gonna get another job. It's okay.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我可以加班  没问题的
I'll take extra shifts. It's not a problem.
完成了  住院医师  替她缝合
Done. Resident, close her up.
持针器
Needle holder.
钳子
Forceps.
-好的  各位  晚安 -晚安
- All right, guys. 'Night. - 'Night.
晚安  医生
'Night, doctor.
晚安  沃伦医生
Good night, Dr. Warren.
晚安
Good night.
我想首要问题是…
I mean, I suppose the primary question is...
这么晚了
You're so late.
我以为你十点就会到家
I thought you were gonna be home by 10:00.
我也这么以为
Yeah. So did I.
手术时间延长了
Surgery ran really long.
我好饿
Well, I'm starving.
我还没吃
I haven't eaten.
为什么?
Why not?
我不确定你想吃什么 你也没回我信息
I wasn't sure what you wanted and you never texted me back.
手术室不能带手机  杰克
I don't have my phone in the or, Jack.
我要是早知道就好了
Well, it'd be nice to know that.
热水器还没修好吗?
Is the hot water still not working?
我打过给维修员  他今天没办法来
Called the guy. He couldn't come today.
好的  不能洗澡就直接睡吧
Okay, well, if I can't take a shower,
别这样
- I gotta go to bed. - Come on.
我一整天没见到你
I haven't gotten to see you all day.
我知道  抱歉  但我真的很累  宝贝
I know, I'm sorry, but I'm really tired, baby.
-跟我跳支舞 -不  杰克  停止
- Dance with me. - No. No, Jack. Just stop.
我刚结束了三十小时的值班
I just finished a 30-hour shift,
我替十二个病人缝合
I sewed up 12 people,
而我在六小时后得回去医院
and I gotta be back in six hours,
我好累
and I'm so tired.
我只想上床睡觉  好吗?
I... I just need to go to bed. Okay?
我想首要问题是…
I mean, I suppose the primary question is...
你认识任何真正快乐的人吗?对吧?
Do you know anyone who's truly happy? Right?
或对生活感到满意?
Or satisfied?
现代社会已扼杀了我们的真实自我
Modern society has smothered our true selves,
让我们脱离生命的缔造
and driven us from, uh, biological destiny.
我看到了你埋藏起来的自我
I see that version of yourself that you've buried deep
被其他人忽略的那个你
and that everyone else ignores.
那才是真实的你
That... that is the real you.
我知道你是你自称的那个人
I know that you are the man you say you are.
这样好多了
That's better.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
看看谁康复了
Look who's feeling better.
哦  谢天谢地!（欢迎回家 爱丽丝小姐）
Oh, thank god!
别对整个社区报告
Okay, don't shout it to the whole neighborhood.
-我来了  -我好想你
- I'm here. - Oh! I missed you so much.
我开始在日记里写八卦
I started writing gossip in a journal.
真的?我该读一读
You did? I should read it then.
-真是悲哀
- So sad. Hi. - Hi!
-哇  你看上去神采奕奕! -谢谢
- Wow, you look sensational! - Thank you.
我感觉好多了
I feel better. I feel good.
-我很高兴你回来了 -我也是
- I'm so happy you're back. - Me, too.
嗨  杰克
Hi, Jack.
-哇!看看这台车   -你喜欢吗?
- Wow! Look at this car. - You like that?
迪恩会爱不释手的
Dean's gonna try to have sex with this vehicle.
迪恩呢?
Where is Dean?
他在跟比尔打高尔夫球
He's playing golf with bill.
亲爱的  你也去吧
Honey, you should go.
你近日来一直在照顾我
All you've been doing is looking after me,
你也该去好好享乐
and you deserve to have some fun.
去吧  把她留给我
Yeah, go. Leave her. She's mine now.
-我们要做园艺  -什么?
- We're gonna garden. - What?
看看植物再喝一杯
Just look at plants and drink.
我才没有花园
- Right. - I don't have a garden.
好吧
Okay!
-再见 -再见
- Bye. - Bye.
♪ You'd be so nice ♪
♪ you'd be paradise ♪
待会儿见
- I'll see you later. Okay. - Mm-hm.
维丽特根本站不起来
Violet would not stand up.
她的屁股好像贴在椅子上
It was like her ass was glued to the chair.
佩吉满脸通红
And peg! Peg's face was so red,
我以为她快爆炸了
I thought her head was gonna pop off.
佩吉是彼得的妻子  她一直都在怀孕
Peg is, um... Peter's wife. Always pregnant.
对  是的
- Right. Yes. Yeah. - Kinda... yeah.
是的  抱歉
Right, okay. Of course. Sorry.
我接受治疗后  思绪不太清晰
My head's been a bit of a blur since the treatment.
没关系
- Yeah. Okay. - It's okay.
-你慢慢会想起的  -对  好的
- It'll all come back to you. - Yeah. Okay.
天啊!
Oh, my goodness!
他们来了
Uh-oh! Here they come.
天啊  嗨!
Oh, my goodness! Hi!
你有看到标牌吗?
Did you see the sign?
那是我一辈子见过最漂亮的标牌!
It is the most beautiful sign I've seen in my life!
你聘请了专业艺术家画的?
Did you hire professional artists to paint it?
-是我们自己画的 -是吗?才不是
- We made it ourselves. - You did? No, you didn't.
快  给我看!
Quick, show me. Come show me!
这部分是我画的
I did this part.
你能指一指吗?哪个部分?快去!
Can you point to it? Which bit? Go! Go! Go!
我画了阳光和字母…
I did the sunshine and the letter...
你画了阳光和…
You did the sunshine and...
控制中有美态
There is beauty in control.
对称中有优雅
There is grace in symmetry.
我们行动一致
We move as one.
控制中有美态
There is beauty in control.
对称中有优雅
There is grace in symmetry.
我们行动一致
We move as one.
控制中有美态  对称中有优雅
There is beauty in control. There is grace in symmetry.
我们行动一致
We move as one.
控制中有美态  对称中有优雅
There is beauty in control. There is grace in symmetry.
我们行动一致
We move as one.
控制中有美态  对称中有优雅
There is beauty in control. There is grace in symmetry.
我们行动一致
We move as one.
嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
-闻起来好香 -谢谢
- It smells amazing. - Thank you.
-你今天过得如何? -我现在不记得了
- How was your day? - I don't even remember now.
很好
Good.
你回来早了…
Well, you're a little early, but I have...
我还有很多事要忙
So many things to finish.
我得把烘炉里的食物取出
So I'm gonna need to go and get things out of the oven.
不  会烤焦的
No, it's gonna burn. No.
我们先吃吧
We'll eat first...
让你补充体力
And that should build up your stamina.
天啊  好美
Oh, my god, that's beautiful.
♪ Darlin' I ♪
“亲爱的”
♪ with you all the time ♪
“我要一直陪着你”
♪ can't you see ♪
“你难道看不出”
“我渴望”“一直陪着你”
♪ with you all the time ♪♪ I long to be ♪
“如今我”
♪ now that I ♪
- ♪ can't you see ♪ - can't you...
♪ with you all the time ♪
“一直陪着你”
-“你难道看不出” -“你难道…”
- ♪ I long to be ♪ - long to be.
-“我渴望” -“渴望”
- ♪ With you all the time ♪ - with you all the time.
-“一直陪着你” -“一直陪着你”
胜利项目  申请人编号426
Victory project, applicant number 426.
姓名为杰克钱伯斯 二十九岁  血型为O阴性
Name: Jack chambers. Age: 29. Blood type: O-negative.
心理评价一般
Psychological evaluation: Fair.
国籍英国
Chosen nationality: British.
妻子为爱丽丝沃伦 已有原先情感关系
Chosen wife: Alice Warren. Pre-existing relationship: Yes.
你是否了解
Do you understand the discretion required
-加入社区所需的酌处权?   -是的
- to be a part of this community? - -Yes.
你是否了解
Do you understand the consequences
-言行失检的后果?   -是的
- of indiscretion? - Yes.
你是否知道你有责任
Are you aware that you are responsible
-准备自己的家庭设备系统?  -是的
- for preparing your home device system? - -Yes.
你是否同意进入胜利社区
Do you consent to the physical and medical
所需的身体和医检规定?
requirements for entry to victory?
是的
Yes.
你是否知道你有责任  为你所选择的妻子进行物理维护?
Are you aware that you are responsible for the physical upkeep of your chosen wife?
是的
Yes.
你是否知道你必须每天
Are you aware that you must exit the simulation
通过胜利总部登出模拟环境
through victory headquarters every day,
并只能在被分配的几小时返回?
and return only for your allotted number of hours?
是的
Yes.
♪ Darlin' I ♪
“亲爱的”
♪ miss you all the time ♪
“我无时无刻都在想你”
♪ can't you see ♪
“你难道看不出”
♪ I long to be ♪
“我渴望”
♪ with you all the time ♪
“一直陪着你”
♪ can't you see ♪
“你难道看不出”
♪ I long to be ♪
“我渴望”
♪ with you all the time ♪
“一直陪着你”
欢迎来到胜利项目
Welcome to the victory project.
目前有七十二位活跃用户
There are currently 72 active users.
你的重新登入已开始
Your reentry has begun.
…平等的主持
The auspice of equality.
我们可以陷入我们所认知的真理
We can fall deeper into what we know is true,
那就是我们都渴望秩序
that we crave order.
我们能屈服于自然界的等级制度吗?
Can we yield to nature's hierarchy?
让你的意识沉入这个世界
Allow your consciousness to sink into this world.
这个真理
Into this truth.
深陷其中  因为事情本该如此
Sink deeper into the way things are supposed to be.
-爱丽丝?  -别靠近!
- Alice? - Don't!
好的
Okay.
宝贝  你的病情又复发了
Baby, you're having another episode.
深呼吸
Just take a deep breath.
没事的  深吸一口气  爱丽丝
- It's okay. Just breathe, Alice.
很好  深吸一口气
That's good. Just breathe.
很好
That's good.
你做了什么?
What did you do?
爱丽丝  请你保持冷静
Alice, please, just stay calm.
没事的  我可以解释
It's gonna be okay. I can explain.
这到底是怎么一回事?
What the fuck is going on?
-看着我  你是我妻子
Look at me, you're my wife.
-到底发生什么事了?  -我爱你
- What the fuck is happening? - I love you. I love you.
不
Oh, no. No.
不  你不能那么说  你根本不爱我
You can't say that. You don't love me.
不  别那么做
-No, don't do that. Don't do that! -You don't love me.
爱丽丝  想想看!
Alice, just think!
想想你的人生以及你真正想要的
Think about your life and what you actually want.
你神经错乱了
- You're psychotic. - Mm-mm.
我有过属于自己的人生
I had a life.
但被你夺走了
You took my life.
不  我拯救了你的人生
No, I saved your life.
-这不属实 -不  听我说
- That's not true. - No, listen to me.
你一天到晚都在工作!
You worked all the time!
我想要工作  也乐在其中!怎么了?
I wanted to work! I loved working! What?
你很痛苦
You were miserable.
也很不开心 你恨透了自己的人生!
You were so unhappy. You hated your life!
那是我的人生!
It was my life!
由我做主的人生!
My life!
你休想夺走!
You don't get to take that from me!
我给你了这个!
I gave this to you!
我给了你这一切  爱丽丝!
I gave you all of this, Alice!
我们很幸运能来到这里!
We are lucky to be here!
法兰克创造了这个世界
Frank built this world
让我们可以过着应得的生活!
so that we can live the life that we deserve!
我必须每天离开
I have to leave every day
去赚足够的钱维持这里的生活
just to make enough money to keep us here,
我憎恶那每一分钟
and I fucking hate every minute of it.
我非常讨厌  爱丽丝!
I fucking hate it, Alice!
你能够留在这里
You get to stay here.
而你很快乐!
And you're happy!
你很快乐
You're happy.
没事的
That's okay.
爱丽丝
Alice.
这里才是最完美的我们
We're perfect in here.
你难道不想跟我一起变得完美吗?
Don't you want to be perfect with me?
不
No. No.
你让我觉得自己疯了
You made me feel like I was crazy.
我向你倾诉…
I came to you...
你却让我以为我该死的疯了
And you made me feel like I was fucking crazy.
爱丽丝  我很抱歉
Alice, I'm so sorry.
但我无需再欺骗你了
But I don't have to lie to you anymore.
爱丽丝…
Alice...
-爱丽丝  求求你  我爱你 -我知道
- Alice, please, I love you. - I know.
你知道我爱你  也愿意为你做任何事
You know I love you. I would do anything for you.
你已占据了我的整个人生
You're my whole life.
我爱你  哦  天啊
I love you. Oh, god.
我们在哪不重要 重要的是我们能在一起It's not about where we are, it's just that we're together.
这是你对我说过的
You said that. You said that to me.
爱丽丝
Alice.
-爱丽丝  我很抱歉 -我的天啊
- Alice, I'm so sorry. - Oh, my god.
还有其他人吗?
Are there others?
跟我一样的人?他们的躯体在哪?
Are there other people like me? Where are their bodies?
-我不知道他们在哪 -天啊
- I don't know where they are. - Oh, god.
我甚至不知道那些男人是谁
I don't know where they are.
我发誓我说的全是真的
I don't even know who the men are. I swear.
这不管我们的事
It's not our business.
男人只需对自己妻子负责  仅此而已
A man's responsible for his own wife and nothing else.
所有的妻子都被困在这里?
So all the wives are trapped here?
天啊  那些孩子
- Oh, my god, the kids. - No.
不  爱丽丝  那些孩子不是真实的
- Oh, my god. - No. No, Alice, the kids aren't real.
-哦天哪
- Oh, god. - They're not real.
-你不用担心他们  这里只有你跟我
Don't worry about them. It's you and me.
看着我 这里只有你跟我
- Look at me. - No, I...
别担心其他人  看着我  只有你跟我
Don't worry about them. Look at me.
看着我 这里只有你跟我
Look at me. It's you and me.
好吗?只有我们两人
Okay? It's you and me.
留在我身边
Stay with me.
-我只需要… -我们会很快乐的
-I just need... mm-hm. -It's okay. We're gonna be happy.
-我需要一点时间 -我们留在这里会很快乐
- I just need a second. - We're gonna be happy here.
- I just need a second. Yeah? - We're gonna be happy.
不  杰克
No, Jack.
不  杰克  求求你
No, Jack, please.
停止  爱丽丝!
Stop. Stop. Alice!
不  我需要一点时间
No, I need a second...
放开我!我没法呼吸!
Get off me! I can't breathe! I can't breathe!
-快放开我! -爱丽丝  快停止!
- Get off me! - Alice, stop it!
-不! -停止  爱丽丝!
- No! No! - Stop it, Alice!
停下
No. No!
停止!
Stop!
爱丽丝?
Alice?
A-Alice?
发生什么事了?
What happened?
怎么了?
What is it?
杰克钱伯斯死了
Jack chambers is dead.
爱丽丝  听我说
Alice, listen to me.
不  我有件事得告诉你
No, I need to tell you something, bunny.
不  你得离开这里
No, you need to leave.
不  这个世界不是真实的
No. This world isn't real.
-爱丽丝 他们会杀了你  -法兰克创建了一个程序
- Alice, they're gonna kill you. - Frank created a program.
-他创造出了一个世界… -我知道
- And he created a world and its... - I know. I know.
他们会杀了你
- And they're gonna kill you. - What?
他们会杀死你真实的身体
They're gonna kill you in the real world.
他们会在真实世界里杀掉你
- They're gonna kill your real body. - What?
-你得离开 -什么?
- You need to go. - What?
知道吗?天啊
Okay? Oh, my god.
爱丽丝  如果一个在这里死去 他在真实世界里也同样会死掉
Alice, if a man dies here, he dies in the real world.
杰克没办法让你重回这个时间点
Jack can't put you back in this time.
他不能像之前那样让你重回
He can't put you back in like he did before.
你现在需要再次登出
You need to exit again, right now.
爱丽丝  你得离开  开杰克的车走!
Alice, you gotta go. You can drive. Take Jack's car!
-去总部  你之前去过了 -邦妮  回答我!
- You need to go to headquarters. - Bunny, answer me!
-你得立即走  爱丽丝! -你说你知道  这是什么意思?
- You need to go right now! - What do you mean, you know?
听我说…
Listen...
我一直都知道
I've always known.
我选择了这样的人生
I chose this.
我的孩子也在这里
My kids are here.
-邦妮  你的孩子不是真实的 -不  他们是真实的
- Bunny, your kids aren't real. - No, they are.
-因为他们在这里是活着的!  -他们不在
- Kids aren't real here. - No, they are.
-不真实  -他们对我来说是真实的  爱丽丝
-Nothing is real. -They're real to me. They're real to me, Alice.
-假的 -他们生活在这
- Nothing... - Because here they're alive!
我在这里没有失去他们
In here, I didn't lose them.
我在这里才能留住他们
Here, I... I can keep them.
你明白吗?
Don't you see?
他们知道吗?
What... do they know?
其他的女人知道吗?
What about the women, do they know?
不
No.
她们不知道
They don't know.
快走
Go.
你必须离开
You have to go.
天啊  爱丽丝  那是谁的血?
Christ, Alice, whose blood is that?
杰克!
Jack!
发生什么事了?杰克呢?迪恩?
What's going on? Where's Jack? Dean?
快回到屋里  爱丽丝  亲爱的  停止
Go back inside, Alice. Sweetheart? Stop.
杰克呢?她在做什么?
Where is Jack? What is she doing?
杰克!
Jack!
亲爱的  我们进屋去吧
Honey, let's go inside.
来吧  我们进屋去
We have to go inside, please.
是孩子们
It's the kids.
杰克呢?
Where is Jack?
佩吉  你得回到屋内去照顾孩子!
Peg. I need you to go inside to the kids, peg!
佩吉  她生病了
Peg, she is unwell.
他们说过不会发生这样的事!
They said nothing like this could happen!
闭嘴  比尔!
Shut up, bill!
他们答应我们会很安全!
They promised it was safe!
杰克!
Jack!
这提醒着我们是谁!
It's a reminder of who we are!
我们来是为了拯救世界
We came to save the world from itself.
我们是承诺的先锋  我们才是未来
We are a vanguard of a promise. We are the future.
我们有着辉煌的兄弟情谊
We are a brotherhood of brilliance,
我们每一个人都是
every single one of us.
接近胜利正门
Approaching victory portal.
准备登出  倒数十  九  八…
Prepare to exit in ten, nine, eight...
-这是谁的世界? -我们的!
- Whose world is this? - Ours!
- Whose world is it? - Ours!
-这是谁的世界? -我们的!
-这是谁的世界? -爱丽丝!
- Whose world is it? - Alice!
快跑  爱丽丝!
Go! Go, Alice! Go!
不!
No, no!
-放开我! -他们会找到你的!
- Get off me! - They'll find you!
求求你  别这么傻!
Please, please, please! Don't be such a fucking...
他们说过不会发生这样的事!
They said it would not happen!
靠!
Fuck!
快阻止她  你们这群白痴!
Stop her, you idiots!
快阻止她!
Stop her!
不!
No, no!
安全级别为红色
Security level is red.
我们在安全的庇护所里
We are under a shelter in place.
留在内并等待进一步的指示
Stay inside and await further instructions.
请注意  胜利社区居民
Attention, victory residents.
安全级别为红色
Security level is red.
她在哪?
Where is she?
发生了严重的车祸
Huge crash.
有两台车和科林斯的车受到撞击 科林斯死了  先生
The two lead cars and Collins. Collins is dead, sir.
给我听好了  别让她离开!
Listen to me, you do not let her exit!
如果她到达那里登出
If she gets there, she gets through.
该由谁让她重回?
Who's gonna put her back in?
法兰克?
Frank?
法兰克  我们该怎么做?先生?
Frank, what do we do? Sir?
你这个愚蠢的男人
You stupid, stupid man.
现在轮到我了
It's my turn now.
不!
No!
快!该死的!
Come on! Shit!
别离开我
Don't leave me.
你和我
You and me.
永远在一起
Always.
你和我
You and me.
我们一旦承认现实…
Once we acknowledge that reality...
我们就能放手
We can let go.
（别担心亲爱的）
♪ It seems we stood and talked ♪
♪ like this before ♪
♪ we looked at each other in the same way then ♪
♪ but I can't remember where ♪
♪ or when ♪
♪ the clothes you're wearing ♪
♪ are the clothes you wore ♪
♪ the smile you are smiling ♪
♪ you were smiling then ♪
♪ but I can't remember where ♪
♪ or when ♪
♪ some things that happened ♪
♪ for the first time ♪
♪ seem to be happening ♪
♪ again ♪
♪ And so it seems ♪
♪ that we've met before ♪
♪ and laughed before ♪
♪ and loved before ♪
♪ but who knows ♪
♪ where ♪
♪ or when ♪
（别担心亲爱的）
♪ Life could be a dream life could be a dream ♪
♪ do do do do, sh-boom ♪
♪ life could be a dream ♪ - ♪ sh-boom ♪
♪ if I could take you up in paradise up above  - ♪ sh-boom ♪
♪ if you would tell me i'm the only one that you love ♪
♪ life could be a dream sweetheart ♪
♪ hello, hello again ♪
♪ sh-boom and hopin' we'll meet again ♪
♪ boom ♪ ba-boom ♪
♪ day dong da ding-dong a-lang-da-lang-da-lang ♪
♪ ah, whoa, whoa, bip ah bi-ba-do-da-dip, whoa ♪
♪ life could be a dream ♪ sh-boom ♪
♪ if only all my precious plans would come true ♪
♪ sh-boom ♪ if you would let me spend my whole life lovin' you ♪
♪ life could be a dream sweetheart ♪
♪ do do do do, sh-boom ♪
♪ every time I look at you ♪
♪ something is on my mind ♪
♪ if you do what I want you to ♪
♪ baby, we'd be so fine ♪
♪ oh, life could be a dream sh-boom ♪
♪ if I could take you up in paradise up above, sh-boom ♪
♪ you'd tell me, darlin' ♪
♪ I'm the only one that you love ♪
♪ life could be a dream sweetheart ♪
♪ hello, hello again ♪
♪ sh-boom and hopin' we'll meet again ♪
♪ boom ♪ ba-boom ♪
♪ day dong da ding-dong a-lang-da-lang-da-lang ♪
♪ ah, whoa, whoa, bip ah bi-ba-do-da-dip, whoa ♪
♪ life could be a dream ♪ sh-boom ♪
♪ life could be a dream sweetheart ♪
♪ Whoa, life could be a dream sh-boom ♪
♪ if I could take you up in paradise up above, sh-boom ♪
♪ you'd tell me, darlin' I'm the only one that you love ♪
♪ life could be a dream sweetheart ♪
♪ hello, hello again ♪
♪ sh-boom and hope we'll meet again, boom ♪ ba-boom ♪
♪ day dong da ding-dong ♪
♪ sha-lang-a-la-lang a-la-lang-a-la-lang-a-la ♪
♪ whoa, whoa, bip ♪
♪ ah Bo da do da dip, whoa ♪
♪ life could be a dream life could be a dream ♪
♪ do do do do, sh-boom ♪